neonisi.com 2009-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Neonisi

The aim of this privacy agreement is to describe the management conditions about personal information on Neonisi and Neonisi-community.  
Neonisi treats all the user’s and guest’s personal information in the full respect of the national Italian normative about privacy and, in particular, of the D. Lgs. 196/2003.  
For further information about the Italian law upon privacy, please visit the official website of the [Warrantor for security of personal information](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/garante/navig/jsp/index.jsp).

### Personal information we collect

Neonisi provides for collecting your personal information with the aim concerning the provision of its own services.  
At the registration, you will be asked for the following identity information: 

  * First name and last name
  * Birth date
  * Address
  * Email address

The fields above are mandatory to register and to create your account on Neonisi. In order to ensure the safest protection of your personal information, Neonisi will ask you to create your user ID (or username) and to fill in twice a password of six characters at least. The user ID chosen while registering will identify you during the employment of Neonisi’s services. Moreover, you will have to insert a secret question and an answer to it, which only you know. These will be asked you to reset the password, in case of lost.

### Use of "cookies"

Neonisi uses cookies in order to keep the connection session, as well as to allow the access to reserved areas and to keep the language and the country chosen, avoiding to select them every time.  
You will be able to refuse cookies, if your browser allow it, but in that case the correct working of Neonisi is not guarantee, in particular for reserved areas.

### How we store your personal information

The most of your personal information will be keep on Neonisi servers until the end of the contractual relationship, in order to allow you to use every service you have required.  
After the definitive disruption of your account, all your personal information will be deleted. With the exception of: 

  * Personal information, which conservation is necessary to fulfill to a specific require of the Judicial Authority
  * Identity information of an undetermined suspended user, kept in order to prevent him to register again.

Those information will be stored by Neonisi exclusively for the purposes above, for a 5 years period.

### Password and secret answer

Neonisi suggest not to reveal to anyone your password or your secret answer. If you decide to provide your user ID, your password or your information to thirds, you will be responsible for every act performed with them. If, for any reason, your password results compromised, we suggest to change it immediately.

### View, check and edit of your personal information

After the registration, you can check and edit the information entered, included: 

  * Your user ID or username
  * Your email address
  * Your registration information
  * Your password
  * Your secret question and answer

Please, update your information, in case of changes.  
Moreover, according to the article 7 of the privacy policy, you deserve the following rights:

  1. The interested party has the right to obtain confirmation of the existence or otherwise of personal data that concerns him, even if the data is not yet recorded, and its transmission in intelligible form.
  2. The interested party has the right to obtain information about:
    1. the source of personal data;
    2. the purposes and methods of its processing;
    3. the logic applied in the case of processing being carried out with recourse to electronic tools;
    4. the identifying details of the controller, the managers and the designated representative outlined in article 5, paragraph 2;
    5. the parties or the categories of parties to whom the personal data can be transmitted or who can get to know it in their capacity as designated representative, in the State territory, of managers or employees.
  3. The interested party has the right to obtain:
    1. the revision, correction or, if there is an interest therein, the integration of the data;
    2. the cancellation, transformation into an anonymous form or the block of data processed in breach of the law, including data that it is not necessary to keep in relation to the purposes for which the data was collected or subsequently processed;
    3. the declaration that the operations set out in points a) and b) have been made known, also as far as their content is concerned, to those to whom the data has been transmitted or diffused, with the exception of the case in which the fulfilment of the former proves to be impossible or involves the use of means that are manifestly out of proportion to the right being safeguarded.
  4. The interested party has the right to object, wholly or partly:
    1. for legitimate reasons to the processing of personal data relating to him, even though it is pertinent to the purpose of its collection;
    2. to the processing of personal data relating to him for the purposes of sending advertising material or for direct selling or for the carrying out of market research or commercial communication.

### Security

Neonisi applies to keep your personal information reserved and confidential, following all the minimal security measures and allowing the access to information only to the direct charged, without pass by thirdly.  
Moreover, Neonisi applies to keep the platform as safe as possible from frauds, checking the users’ identity and ruling out the trespasser.

### Notice

Neonisi deserves the right to change the present agreement upon privacy without any previous advice. These changes will be operative immediately since their publication.

### Treatment owner

The treatment owner of your personal information is:

Neonisi s.r.l.  
Via Marcona 49  
20129 Milan, Italy  
VAT: 06734040964
